http://www.dewittobserver.com/site/privacy.html

Home
The following privacy policy governs the DeWitt Observer's online collection of information from you. This privacy policy, including our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means; for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail. We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply to us online as part of the Service. We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as users navigate online through the Service. Unless you inform us otherwise, dewittobserver.com reserves the right to use, and to disclose to third parties, information collected from you while you are using the Service (e.g., your name and e-mail address) for a variety of reasons and purposes, such as providing users with information about products and services. If you do not wish to be included in such uses, you must send an e-mail or a letter to us requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be given or sold to third party vendors.In addition, please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example in online contests, through email, or in other inactive areas, that information can be collected and used by others besides dewittobserver.com. dewittobserver.com cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third party use of information that you disclose online.We use "cookies" in a limited way to help deliver advertisements and to identify subscribers and readers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site. Some of our business affiliates and advertisers use cookies, which can be used to tell when your computer has contacted a web site. Because we do not control the privacy policies of our business affiliates, advertisers or any other sites to which we may provide hyperlinks, you should check the privacy policy of the site you are visiting if you have any concerns about that site's use of cookies or about that site's use of your information.We also make some content, products and services available through our Service through cooperative relationships with third party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear prominently on the Service. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner's use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider directly for more information.Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of our Services, the public, or dewittobserver.com.Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we, some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information on our users may be among the transferred assets.Children's Privacy Statement for dewittobserver.comThis children's privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information on your rights under federal law with respect to such information.We do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service.Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Service.Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we do NOT condition the participation in the Service's online activities of a child under thirteen on providing personally identifiable information.Google Analytics AddendumThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files saved on your computer, to help the website analyze how you use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. If this website anonymizes IP addresses, your IP address will be truncated by Google within a EU member state or other EEA state before being transmitted to the US. Only in exceptional situations will your full IP address be transmitted to Google servers in the United States and truncated there. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You can also prevent Google from collecting information (including your IP address) via cookies and processing this information by downloading this browser plugin and installing it: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptoutYou can prevent data collection via Google Analytics by clicking here. An "Opt-out Cookie" shall then be applied to your website which shall prevent any future collection of your data when visiting this website.Further information concerning the terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at the Google Analytics Terms of Service or at the Google Analytics Privacy Overview. Please note that on this website, Google Analytics is supplemented by "gat._anonymizeIp();" to ensure anonymized collection of IP addresses (IP masking).Questions on PrivacyIf you have any questions about the children's privacy statement, the privacy practices of dewittobserver.com, or your dealings with dewittobserver.com, you can contact:Sycamore MediaDigital Media Services108 W. Quarry St.Maquoketa, IA 52060webmanager@sycamoremedia.net563.652.2441
Latest Print Edition
The Observer
To view our latest edition click the image on the left.
Christmas Cuties
Surprise your Christmas Cutie with their picture in the Wednesday, Dec. 16th Observer. All of the children's photographs along with family information will be placed on consecutive pages in alphabetical order. Just click on the button below to complete the form. The cost is $7 per child.
SUBMIT YOUR CUTIE NOW
Local Forecast
DeWitt, IA
Right Now
37°
Clear
Humidity: 81%
Feels Like: 33°
Heat Index: 37°
Wind:
5 mph
Wind Chill: 33°
UV Index: 0 Low
Sunrise: 07:19:29 AM
Sunset: 04:31:03 PM
Dew Point: 31°
Visibility: 8 mi
Today
Mostly clear this evening then becoming cloudy after midnight. Low 33F. Winds NNE at 10 to 15 mph.
Tonight
Mostly clear this evening then becoming cloudy after midnight. Low 33F. Winds NNE at 10 to 15 mph.
Tomorrow
Periods of rain. High 41F. Winds NE at 10 to 20 mph. Chance of rain 100%. Rainfall near a half an inch.
UpcomingRadar7 Day
Next 12 Hours
Time
Temp
Wind
Precip
12 AM
36°
Fareway
To view the latest Fareway Circular click the image on the left.
Latest Special Sections
Country Life Fall 2020
To view our latest Special Section click the image on the left.
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesFieldstone site work beginsWarriors girls come through late, top RebelsUS House may decide winner in Iowa’s 2nd District: What’s next and how we got hereThomas Michael GarrityTrail connecting Calamus and Wheatland could become realityScott-Munro will wed in April 2021Iowa COVID-19 cases increase by 5,151 over the weekend to 244,844; 114 additional deaths; Clinton adds 80 casesCOVID complaints should be sent to stateMyrna M. Cavanagh23 deaths from COVID-19 reported in Woodbury County since Thanksgiving
ImagesSorry, there are no recent results for popular images.
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Follow us on Facebook
dewittobserver
